There is no plan B.
The A-Team is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Joe Carnahan.
A man who loves when a plan comes together, Col.
Hannibal Smith leads a close-knit team of elite
operatives and Iraq War veterans.
Framed for a crime they didn't commit, Smith and his men, Capt.
‘Howling Mad’ Murdock , Sgt.
Bosco ‘B.A.’ Baracus, and Lt.
Templeton ‘Faceman’ Peck, break out and go rogue, using their special
talents to clear their names and find the perpetrator.
Hot on their trail is Capt.
Charissa Sosa, who was once involved with a member of Smith's team and
has sworn to capture them, no matter what it takes.
Hannibal, played by Liam Neeson.
Face, played by Bradley Cooper.
Charisa Sosa, played by Jessica Biel.
B.A. Baracus, played by Quinton 'Rampage' Jackson.
Murdock, played by Sharlto Copley.
Lynch, played by Patrick Wilson.
The A-Team is a 2010 American action comedy film based on the 1980s television
series of the same name created by Frank Lupo and Stephen J.
Directed by Joe Carnahan and written by Carnahan, Brian Bloom, and Skip Woods, the film stars Liam
Neeson, Bradley Cooper, Jessica Biel, Quinton Jackson, Sharlto Copley, and Patrick Wilson.
The film tells the story of a Special Forces team who, imprisoned for a crime
they did not commit, escapes and sets out to clear their names.
The film was produced by Cannell, Tony Scott, and (as
executive producer) his brother Ridley Scott.
The film had been in development since the mid-1990s having gone through a number
of writers and story ideas and being put on hold a number of times.
Neeson, Cooper, and the rest of the cast joined in summer 2009, and
filming took place around Canada later that year.
The film was theatrically released on June 11, 2010, by 20th Century Fox.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who praised the cast
and action sequences but criticized the script.
A sequel was initially anticipated, but as the film underperformed at the box office, grossing
$177 million worldwide against its $110 million budget, plans were scrapped.
The film explores themes of plan, mexico, explosive, war crimes, secret mission.
The tone is lighthearted.